First time to go to Chinese Ice Cream
Hello, my name is Priya and today is our first day in China.
in
And as the day began, our settlers collided with this car.
went
But no matter, we got to TMN Square and here on every
There's a camera in the corner, brother
So we have this trip to the parents' seat,
There was a vibe
Then we walked down TMN Square to the Forbidden.
City
Here we go in a straight line.
And the Forbidden City is 600 years old.
And the entrance was so beautiful, so grand.
It was a one-time thing, so let's get ice cream.
Let's eat
And inside the Forbidden City was a shop of ice cream.
And then when I open it, it'll give me the first thing.
I am
When I put the ice cream in a loose sea tray
I'm eating
So cute, then I took the first bait, maybe it was heat.
So I was so fond of ten corners.
But use so cream and milk
Then we sat in a bus and had lunch.
gone
We loaded the Vesterbull Dumpling with a little bit of chili oil.
I was hungry too, but seven oats were tight.
The stomach is full
Today I go to Chinese ice cream for the first time.